Ralph Ellis Search for Tomorrow Collection
Ralph Ellis Search for Tomorrow Collection
- Studio and Draft scripts
  - 5521 Studio Script, 12/7/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5522 Studio Script, 12/8/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5523 Studio Script, 12/11/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5524 Studio Script, 12/12/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5525 Studio Script, 12/13/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5526 Studio Script, 12/14/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5527 Studio Script, 12/15/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5528 Studio Script, 12/18/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5529 Studio Script, 12/19/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5530 Studio Script, 12/20/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5531 Studio Script, 12/21/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5532 Studio Script, 12/22/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5533 Studio Script, 12/25/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5534 Studio Script, 12/26/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5535 Studio Script, 12/27/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5536 Studio Script, 12/28/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5537 Studio Script, 12/29/1972 (Box 6)
  - 5538 Studio Script, 1/2/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5538-5539 Studio Script, 1/2/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5539 Studio Script, 1/3/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5540 Studio Script, 1/4/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5541 Draft Script, 1/5/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5542 Studio Script, 1/8/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5543 Studio Script, 1/9/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5544 Studio Script, 1/10/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5545 Studio Script, 1/11/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5546 Studio Script, 1/12/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5547 Studio Script, 1/15/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5548 Studio Script, 1/16/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5549 Draft Script, 1/17/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5550 Draft Script, 1/18/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5551 Draft Script, 1/19/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5552 Draft Script, 1/22/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5553 Draft Script, 1/23/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5554 Draft Script, 1/24/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5555 Draft Script, 1/25/1873 (Box 6)
  - 5556 Draft Script, 1/26/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5557 Draft Script, 1/29/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5558 Draft Script, 1/30/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5559 Draft Script, 1/31/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5560 Draft Script, 2/1/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5561 Draft Script, 2/2/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5562 Draft Script, 2/5/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5563 Draft Script, 2/6/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5564 Draft Script, 2/7/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5565 Draft Script, 2/8/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5566 Draft Script, 2/9/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5567 Draft Script, 2/12/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5568 Draft Script, 2/13/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5569 Draft Script, 2/14/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5570 Draft Script, 2/15/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5571 Draft Script, 2/16/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5572 Draft Script, 2/19/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5573 Draft Script, 2/20/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5574 Studio Script, 2/21/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5575 Draft Script, 2/22/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5576 Draft Script, 2/23/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5577 Draft Script, 2/26/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5578 Draft Script, 2/27/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5579 Studio Script, 2/28/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5580 Studio Script, 3/1/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5581 Studio Script, 3/3/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5582 Studio Script, 3/5/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5583 Studio Script, 3/6/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5584 Draft Script, 3/7/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5585 Draft Script, 3/8/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5586 Draft Script, 3/9/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5587 Draft Script, 3/12/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5588 Draft Script, 3/13/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5589 Studio Script, 3/14/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5590 Studio Script, 3/15/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5591 Draft Script, 3/16/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5592 Draft Script, 3/19/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5593 Draft Script, 3/20/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5594 Draft Script, 3/21/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5595 Draft Script, 3/22/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5596 Studio Script, 3/23/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5597 Draft Script, 3/26/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5598 Draft Script, 3/27/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5599 Draft Script, 3/28/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5600 Draft Script, 3/29/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5601 Draft Script, 3/30/1973 (Box 6)
  - 5602 Draft Script, 1/2/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5603 Draft Script, 4/3/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5604 Draft Script, 4/4/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5605 Draft Script, 4/5/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5606 Draft Script, 4/6/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5607 Draft Script, 4/9/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5608 Draft Script, 4/10/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5609 Draft Script, 4/11/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5610 Draft Script, 4/12/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5611 Draft Script, 4/13/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5612 Draft Script, 4/16/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5613 Draft Script, 4/17/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5614 Draft Script, 4/18/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5615 Draft Script, 4/19/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5616 Draft Script, 4/20/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5617 Draft Script, 4/23/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5618 Draft Script, 4/24/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5619 Draft Script, 4/25/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5620 Draft Script, 4/26/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5621 Draft Script, 4/27/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5622 Draft Script, 4/30/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5623 Draft Script, 5/1/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5624 Draft Script, 5/2/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5625 Draft Script, 5/3/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5626 Draft Script, 5/4/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5627 Draft Script, 5/7/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5631 Draft Script, 5/11/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5681 Draft Script, Acts I and II, 7/26/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5682 Draft Script, Act II, 7/27/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5685 Draft Script, Act III, 8/1/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5686 Draft Script, Acts I and II, 8/2/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5690 Draft Script, Acts I and II, 8/8/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5690 Studio Script, 8/8/1974 (Box 6)
  - 5691 Draft Script, 8/9/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5691 Studio Script, 8/9/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5692 Studio Script, 8/10/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5692 Draft Script, 8/10/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5693 Draft Script, 8/13/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5693 Studio Script, 8/13/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5694 Studio Script, 8/14/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5695 Studio Script, 8/15/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5696 Draft Script, 8/16/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5696 Studio Script, 8/16/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5697 Studio Script, 8/20/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5698 Studio Script, 8/21/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5699 Studio Script, 8/22/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5700 Studio Script, 8/23/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5701 Studio Script, 8/24/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5702 Studio Script, 8/27/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5703 Studio Script, 8/28/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5704 Studio Script, 8/29/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5705 Studio Script, 8/30/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5706 Studio Script, 8/31/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5707 Studio Script, 9/3/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5708 Studio Script, 9/4/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5709 Studio Script, 9/5/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5710 Studio Script, 9/6/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5711 Studio Script, 9/7/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5712 Studio Script, 9/10/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5713 Studio Script, 9/11/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5714 Studio Script, 9/12/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5715 Studio Script, 9/13/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5716 Studio Script, 9/14/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5717 Studio Script, 9/17/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5718 Studio Script, 9/18/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5719 Studio Script, 9/19/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5720 Studio Script, 9/20/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5721 Studio Script, 9/21/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5722 Studio Script, 9/24/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5723 Studio Script, 9/25/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5723 Draft Script, 9/25/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5724 Studio Script, 9/26/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5725 Studio Script, 9/27/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5726 Studio Script, 9/28/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5727 Studio Script, 10/1/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5728 Studio Script, 10/2/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5729 Draft Script, 10/3/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5729 Studio Script, 10/3/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5730 Studio Script, 10/4/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5731 Studio Script, 10/5/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5732 Studio Script, 10/8/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5733 Studio Script, 10/9/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5734 Studio Script, 10/10/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5735 Studio Script, 10/11/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5736 Studio Script, 10/12/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5738 Studio Script, 10/16/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5739 Studio Script, 10/17/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5740 Studio Script, 10/18/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5741 Studio Script, 10/19/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5742 Studio Script, 10/22/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5743 Studio Script, 10/23/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5744 Studio Script, 10/24/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5745 Studio Script, 10/25/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5746 Studio Script, 10/26/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5747 Studio Script, 10/29/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5748 Studio Script, 10/30/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5749 Studio Script, 10/31/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5750 Studio Script, 11/1/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5751 Studio Script, 11/2/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5752 Studio Script, 11/5/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5753 Studio Script, 11/6/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5754 Studio Script, 11/7/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5755 Studio Script, 11/8/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5756 Studio Script, 11/12/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5757 Studio Script, 11/13/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5758 Studio Script, 11/14/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5759 Studio Script, 11/15/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5760 Studio Script, 11/16/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5761 Studio Script, 11/19/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5762 Studio Script, 11/21/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5763 Studio Script, 11/23/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5764 Studio Script, 11/26/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5765 Studio Script, 11/27/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5766 Studio Script, 11/28/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5767 Studio Script, 11/29/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5768 Studio Script, 11/30/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5769 Studio Script, 12/3/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5770 Studio Script, 12/4/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5771 Studio Script, 12/5/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5772 Studio Script, 12/6/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5773 Studio Script, 12/7/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5774 Draft Script, 12/10/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5775 Draft Script, 12/11/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5776 Draft Script, 12/12/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5777 Draft Script, 12/13/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5778 Studio Script, 12/14/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5779 Studio Script, 12/17/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5780 Studio Script, 12/18/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5781 Studio Script, 12/19/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5782 Studio Script, 12/20/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5783 Studio Script, 12/21/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5784 Draft Script, 12/24/1974 (Box 7)
  - 5785 Studio Script, 12/25/1974 (Box 7)